Finding aid to the Classes of 1911-1920 records CA.MS.01018
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1911-1920 records
1895-1997
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1911.
CA.MS.01018
199.5 linear feet (292 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1911-1920 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College--Alumni and alumnae; Smith College -- Students; Smith College. Class of 1912.; Smith College. Class of 1913.; Smith College. Class of 1914.; Smith College. Class of 1915.; Smith College. Class of 1916.; Smith College. Class of 1917.; Smith College. Class of 1918.; Smith College. Class of 1919.; Smith College. Class of 1920.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae; Smith College--Students.
- Class of 1911 Records, 1907-1976; 12.625 linear feet (22 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1911 was the thirty-third entering class and the thirty-third graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1911 records, 1907-1976, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1911, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 1)
  - Bat, 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 2)
  - Collation, 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Grind, 1907 (Box 1771, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1907 (Box 1771, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1907 (Box 1771, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1907-1911 (Box 1771, Folder 9)
  - History, 1907-1961 (Box 1772, Folder 2)
  - Insignia, Numerals, undated (Box 1772, Folder 1)
  - Ivy Day, 1911 (Box 1772, Folder 3)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1911 (Box 1772, Folder 4)
  - Junior Prom, 1910 (Box 1772, Folder 5)
  - Junior Prom Garden Party, 1910 (Box 1772, Folder 6)
  - Junior Ushers, 1910 (Box 1772, Folder 7)
  - Class Letters, 1911-1976 (Box 1773, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, General, undated (Box 1773, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1912-1913 (Box 1773, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1914 (Box 1773, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1916 (Box 1773, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1921-1925 (Box 1773, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1928-1931 (Box 1773, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1936 (Box 1773, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1773, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 1773, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 1773, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 1773, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 1773, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1975-1976 (Box 1773, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1966-1976 (Box 1773, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1981 (Box 1773, Folder 16)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1773, Folder 17)
  - Reunion scrapbook (Box 1776.1)
  - Senior Dramatics- Music, 1911 (Box 1773, Folder 18)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 3)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1774, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1909 (Box 1774, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, undated (Box 1774, Folder 6)
  - Statistics- War Service, 1941-1946 (Box 1774, Folder 7)
  - Class Supper, 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 8)
  - Year Book, 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified, 1960; undated (Box 1774, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Records, A-Bar (Box 1775, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Bas-Br (Box 1775, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Bu-C (Box 1775, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Col-El (Box 1775, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Est-God (Box 1775, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Go-Hu (Box 1775, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Records, I-Little (Box 1775, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Lloyd-Mills (Box 1775, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Mo-Pat (Box 1775, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Pe-Ri (Box 1775, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Ro-She (Box 1776, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Records, Shi-Tho (Box 1776, Folder 2)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 1777)
  - Individuals E-L (Box 1778)
  - Individuals M-P (Box 1779)
  - Individuals Q-Watters (Box 1780)
  - Individuals Watters-Wilbur (Box 1781)
  - Individuals Williams-Z (Box 1782)
  - Baker, Florence Matthews (photo album) (Box 1783)
  - Blanche Buttfield Pratt reunion memorabilia, class scrapbook, 1921-1971; 2017-A-0158; Reynolds, Jane Pratt; Buttfield, Blanche, Class of 1911; 1 folders (1 folder in a legal document box containing multiple accessions) (Box CA Shared 1)
    Photographs, correspondence, lists of attendees of the Class of 1911's reunions, in particular, the 50th and 60th reunion.
    photographs; Reynolds, Jane Pratt
  - Bodwell, Bertha Tamenia (photo album) (Box 1783)
  - Brown, Helen Gould (memorabilia book) (Box 1786.1)
  - Goddard, Eleanor Grace (photo album) (Box 1783)
  - Goddard, Eleanor G. (scrapbook) (Box 1786.5)
  - Hooper, Catharine Baker (memorabilia book) (Box 1784)
  - Lowndes, Helen Stanley (memorabilia book) (Box 1785)
  - Martin, Jane Culbertson (memorabilia book) (Box 1786.3)
  - Rosenthal, Aline (scrapbook) (Box 1786.5)
  - Southard, Elizabeth (memorabilia book) (Box 1786.4)
  - Townsend, Margaret (photo album) (Box 1786.4)
  - Wilber, Laura Elizabeth (memorabilia book) (Box 1786)
- Class of 1912 Records, 1908-1982; 28.875 linear feet (46 containers)
  The Class of 1912 was the thirty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1912 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1912, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 1)
  - Class Baby, undated (Box 1787, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1912-1913 (Box 1787, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 7)
  - Expense Account Journal, 1908-1913 (Box 1787, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1908 (Box 1787, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1908 (Box 1787, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Grind, 1908 (Box 1787, Folder 11)
  - Groups, 1908-1912 (Box 1787, Folder 12)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 14)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 15)
  - Junior Prom, 1911 (Box 1787, Folder 16)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1911 (Box 1787, Folder 17)
  - Junior Ushers, 1911 (Box 1787, Folder 18)
  - Class Letters, 1920-1982 (Box 1787, Folder 19)
  - Seal, Emblem, etc., undated (Box 1787, Folder 20)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1909 (Box 1787, Folder 21)
  - Step Sings, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 22)
  - Class Songs, undated (Box 1787, Folder 23)
  - Class Supper, 1912 (Box 1787, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1913-1914 (Box 1788, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1915-1916 (Box 1788, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1917 (Box 1788, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1927 (Box 1788, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1932 (Box 1788, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 1788, Folder 6)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1937 (Box 1788, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1937 (Box 1788, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1937 (Box 1788, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1789, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 1789, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 1789, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 1789, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 1789, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 1789, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 1789, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 1789, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 1789, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 1789, Folder 10)
  - Reunions-Songs, undated (Box 1789, Folder 11)
  - Reunions-Publications, "Gas Bag", 1920-1938 (Box 1789, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1912-1928 (Box 1789, Folder 13)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1912 (Box 1790, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Business Manager's Report, 1912 (Box 1790, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics-Committee Report, 1912 (Box 1790, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1912 (Box 1790, Folder 4)
  - Reunion Costumes (Box 1790.1)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 1791)
  - Individuals E-M (Box 1792)
  - Individuals N-Se (Box 1793)
  - Individuals Sh-T (Box 1794)
  - Individuals U-Z (Box 1795)
  - Battles, Beth (memorabilia book) (Box 1816.1)
  - Bartholomew, Helen Gertrude (memorabilia book) (Box 1816.2)
  - Carpenter, Frances Aretta (photo albums, papers) (Box 1796)
  - Clapp, Marie Antoinette (biographical) (Box 1797)
  - Clapp, Marie Antoinette (correspondence) (Box 1798)
  - Clapp, Marie Antoinette (memorabilia book and class notes) (Box 1799)
  - Comstock, Edith Clare (photo album) (Box 1816.2)
  - Comstock, Edith Claire (memorabilia book, Class secretary's album and scrapbook) (Box 1816.3)
  - Doremus, Nell Budlong (memorabilia book) (Box 1802)
  - Doremus, Nell Budlong (memorabilia book) (Box 1803)
  - Edwards, Hilda Blanche (memorabilia book) (Box 1816.4)
  - Edwards, Hilda Blanche (memorabilia book) (Box 1816.5)
  - Emerson, Louise Kingman (memorabilia book) (Box 1804)
  - Emerson, Louise Kingman (memorabilia book) (Box 1805)
  - Espy, (Laura) Frances (memorabilia books) (Box 1816.6)
  - Fink, Eugenie (class notes) (Box 1805.1)
  - Frankenstein, Sally Moss (memorabilia book) (Box 1806)
  - Hedrick, Florence (scrapbook) (Box 1806.1)
  - Herman, Maida (memorabilia book, misc.) (Box 1807)
  - Hopkins, Hester Adams (correspondence) (Box 1808)
  - Hopkins, Hester Adams (Box 1808.1)
  - Houghton, Helen Wetmore (photo album) (Box 1816.7)
  - Lange, Florence Elizabeth (memorabilia books) (Box 1816.9)
  - Marble, Sarah Almy (photo albums) (Box 1816.10)
  - Martin, Cyrena Van Syckel (class notes, photos) (Box 1809)
  - Martin, Cyrena Van Syckel (class notes - chemistry, english, geometry, logic) (Box 1810)
  - Martindale, Katharine (memorabilia book) (Box 1811)
  - Michael, Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1816.5)
  - Michael, Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1816.8)
  - Michael, Louise (photo album) (Box 1816.7)
  - O'Meary, Lucy (photo album) (Box 1812)
  - Ordway, Priscilla (memorabilia book) (Box 1813)
  - Pierson, Marion Ethel (photo album) (Box 1816.10)
  - Rich, Cecile Rae (memorabilia book and photograph album) (Box 1814)
  - Shapleigh, Margaret (memorabilia book) (Box 1815)
  - Shapleigh, Margaret (photograph album) (Box 1815.1)
  - Talbot, Mary (photo album, class memorabilia book) (Box 1816.11)
  - Webster, Elizabeth Howland (correspondence) (Box 1816)
  - Williams, Edith Louise (photograph album) (Box 1816.12)
  - Williams, Olive (memorabilia book and Dramatics album) (Box 1816.13)
- Class of 1913 Records, 1909-1980; 22.958 linear feet (42 containers)
  The Class of 1913 was the thirty-fourth entering class and the thirty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1913 records, 1909-1980, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1913, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia. The Class Secretary's files also contain individual biographical information.
  - Baccalaureate, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 1)
  - Distinguished Members, 1949-1950 (Box 1817, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 3)
  - Clippings-Hampshire Gazette, June 17, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary-Obituaries (Box 1817, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Music, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 8)
  - Constitution, undated (Box 1817, Folder 9)
  - County Fair, 1912 (Box 1817, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1909 (Box 1817, Folder 11)
  - Freshman Grind, 1909 (Box 1817, Folder 12)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1909 (Box 1817, Folder 13)
  - Groups, 1909-1913 (Box 1817, Folder 14)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 15)
  - Ivy Day, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 16)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 17)
  - Junior Frolic, 1912 (Box 1818, Folder 1)
  - Junior Prom, 1912 (Box 1818, Folder 2)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1912 (Box 1818, Folder 3)
  - Class Letters, 1923-1944 (Box 1818, Folder 4)
  - Class Letters, 1945-1964 (Box 1818, Folder 5)
  - Class Letters, 1965-1980 (Box 1818, Folder 6)
  - Class Photographs, 1913; 1926 (Box 1821.1)
  - Class Scrapbook, Photo Album (Box 1821.2)
  - Class Scrapbook, Reunion Memorabilia (Box 1821.3)
  - Seal Emblem, undated (Box 1818, Folder 7)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 8)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 9)
  - Senior Reception, 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 10)
  - Class Supper, 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 11)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1911 (Box 1818, Folder 12)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1818, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Vespers, 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters-A-B, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 1)
  - Class Letters-C-D, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 2)
  - Class Letters-E-G, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 3)
  - Class Letters-H-K, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 4)
  - Class Letters-L-M, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 5)
  - Class Letters-O-R, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 6)
  - Class Letters-S-T, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 7)
  - Class Letters-U-Z, 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Records-A-B (Box 1819, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Records-C-D (Box 1819, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Records-E-G (Box 1819, Folder 11)
  - Class Secretary's Records-H-K (Box 1819, Folder 12)
  - Class Secretary's Records-L-N (Box 1819, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Records-O-R (Box 1819, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Records-S-T (Box 1819, Folder 15)
  - Class Secretary's Records-V-Z (Box 1819, Folder 16)
  - Reunions-Secretary's Notebooks, 1909-1958 (Box 1820, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1914-1915 (Box 1820, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1923 (Box 1820, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1928 (Box 1820, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 1820, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 1820, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1820, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Composita Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 2)
  - Reunions-Composita Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 3)
  - Reunions-Composita Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-Composita Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 1821, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1821, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1973 (Box 1821, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 1821, Folder 9)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1821, Folder 10)
  - Reunion Memorabilia, 1938 (Box 1821.4)
  - Individuals Ar-Col (Box 1822)
  - Individuals A-Ar (Box 1822.1)
  - Individuals Con-Gi (Box 1823)
  - Individuals Go-Hal (Box 1824)
  - Individuals Har-Hig (Box 1825)
  - Individuals Hin-L (Box 1826)
  - Individuals M-Sh (Box 1827)
  - Individuals Si-Z (Box 1828)
  - Bailey, Gladys V. (scrapbook) (Box 1828.1)
  - Barnum, Helen Adelaide (memorabilia books) (Box 1828.2)
  - Barnum, Helen Adelaide (scrapbook) (Box 1828.3)
  - Carr, Katherine (memorabilia book) (Box 1829)
  - Chamberlain, Emily Hazard (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1829)
  - Coit, Jessie B. (correspondence, photographs, misc.) (Box 1830)
  - Coit, Jessie B. (memorabilia book) (Box 1830.1)
  - Cone, Alice Weston (lab notebook - Botany) (Box 1829)
  - Cory, Eleanor Lansing (scrapbook), 1909; Accession 2018-A-0080; Eleanor Lansing Cory; Deborah Sandler; .5 linear feet (1 flat box) (Box 1830.2)
    Memorabilia of Cory's first year at Smith College; includes paper items, photographs, pressed leaves, and miscellaneous objects
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of Deborah Sandler
    Deborah Sandler
  - Fisher, Fronia Ernestine (memorabilia books) (Box 1844.2)
  - Greene, Elizabeth (correspondence) (Box 1831)
  - Halsey, Marion Spencer (correspondence) (Box 1832)
  - Halsey, Marion Spencer (photo albums of Red Cross and missionary work) (Box 1833)
  - Halsey, Marion Spencer (class notes) (Box 1834)
  - Hodgman, Helen Emerson (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1836)
  - Hodgman, Helen (memorabilia book) (Box 1828.2)
  - Knox, Marguerite (memorabilia book) (Box 1844.3)
  - Jackson, Lilian (correspondence, photos, account book) (Box 1837)
  - Jones, Dorothy Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1838)
  - La Gassee, Grace, ex-1913 (scrapbook) (Box 1838.1)
  - MacFarland, Lena Elizabeth (memorabilia book) (Box 1839)
  - Mather, Annie Elizabeth (photograph album) (Box 1844.5)
  - McQuigg, Winifred Moore (memorabilia book) (Box 1844.4)
  - Schlosser, Elizabeth (miscellaneous post-college) (Box 1842)
  - Edith Weck, Class of 1913, papers, approximately 1895-1913; 2018-A-0064; 1 linear feet (1 record carton)
    scrapbook, photograph album, loose photographs, negatives, and Class of 1913 publications documenting her undergraduate years
    Donated by Karl Johnson, relative of Weck
    - Scrapbook of years at Smith College, 1909-1913; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)
    - Photograph album of childhood and Smith College, approximately 1895-1913; 1 items (1 item) (Box 1)
    - Loose photographs, approximately 1913; 6 items 6 photographs (1 folder) (Box 1)
    - Negatives, approximately 1913; 1 folders (1 envelope) (Box 1)
  - Williamson, Clara Roulstone (memorabilia book) (Box 1843)
  - Winslow, Mina Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1843)
  - Wyeth, Sara Campbell (memorabilia book) (Box 1844)
  - Wyeth, Sara Campbell (memorabilia book) (Box 1844.1)
  - Wyeth, Sara Campbell (photograph books) (Box 1844.5)
  - Reunion photograph (Box 1920.5)
- Class of 1914 Records, 1910-1985; 24.042 linear feet (38 containers)
  The Class of 1914 was the thirty-fifth entering class and the thirty-fifth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1914 records, 1910-1985, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1914, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia. The Class Secretary's Notes contain biographical material as well as a necrology.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1910 (Box 1845, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Grind, 1910 (Box 1845, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1910 (Box 1845, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1910-1914 (Box 1845, Folder 8)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 14)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1914 (Box 1845, Folder 15)
  - Junior Frolic, 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 12)
  - Junior Ushers, 1913 (Box 1845, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1927-1957 (Box 1845.1, Folder 16)
  - Class Letters, 1958-1985 (Box 1845.1, Folder 17)
  - Class Officers, 1910-1974 (Box 1845.1, Folder 18)
  - Necrology, undated (Box 1846)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology (Box 1846, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology (Box 1846, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology, 1969 (Box 1846, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-A (Box 1846, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-B (Box 1846, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-C (Box 1846, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-D (Box 1846, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-E (Box 1846, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-F (Box 1846, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-G (Box 1846, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-H (Box 1846, Folder 11)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-I-J (Box 1846, Folder 12)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-K (Box 1846, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-L (Box 1846, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-M (Box 1846, Folder 15)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-N (Box 1846, Folder 16)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-O (Box 1846, Folder 17)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-P (Box 1846, Folder 18)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-Q (Box 1846, Folder 19)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-R (Box 1846, Folder 20)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-S (Box 1846, Folder 21)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-T (Box 1846, Folder 22)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-U-V (Box 1846, Folder 23)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-W (Box 1846, Folder 24)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Necrology-X-Z (Box 1846, Folder 25)
  - Class Secretary's Records (Box 1847, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-A (Box 1847, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-B (Box 1847, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-C (Box 1847, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-D (Box 1847, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-E (Box 1847, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-F (Box 1847, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-G (Box 1847, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-H (Box 1847, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-I-J (Box 1847, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-K (Box 1847, Folder 11)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-L (Box 1847, Folder 12)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Mc-M (Box 1847, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-N (Box 1847, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-O (Box 1847, Folder 15)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-P (Box 1847, Folder 16)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Q (Box 1847, Folder 17)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-R (Box 1847, Folder 18)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-S (Box 1847, Folder 19)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-T (Box 1847, Folder 20)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-U-V (Box 1847, Folder 21)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-W (Box 1847, Folder 22)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-X-Z (Box 1847, Folder 23)
  - Photograph Albums, undated (Box 1848, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Albums, undated (Box 1848, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Material-General (Box 1849, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1915 (Box 1849, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1917 (Box 1849, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1919 (Box 1849, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1924 (Box 1849, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1929 (Box 1849, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 1849, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 1849, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 1849, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 1849, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1849, Folder 11)
    General
    (see also Box 1850)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 1849, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1849, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 1849, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 1849, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 1849, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Questionnaire, 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 3)